<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Janset Askin</title>
    <link>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Janset Askin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m Janset Askin. I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Scientist with an interest in machine learning engineering and ethical AI. I have experience with full-stack data science work including data extraction, explanatory data analysis, feature engineering, model development and validation, and model deployment using MLOps principles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/experience/</guid>
      <description>Technical Skills  Programming: Python, R Data Science: SQL, Git, Tableau, pandas, NumPy, matplotlib, scikit-learn, pytest, Plotly, Dash Development: Flask, Postman, Jenkins, Docker, AWS (S3, EC2, CloudWatch) CLI, Shell Scripting, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, code profiling Machine Learning: Natural Language Processing, Linear/Logistic Regression, Random Forest, K-Means, Naive Bayes, PCA, SVM, GBM, Multi-Class Classification, Imbalanced Data   Work Experience Data Scientist, Progressive Insurance June 2021 - Present
 Build an algorithm for artist to detect if their music was violating copyright infringement laws Successfully won Techcrunch Disrupt Optimized an algorithm that holds the current world record for Weisman Scores Built full stack natural language processing model to classify 300+ categories for various business products to classify business class and deployed API to serve model in cloud with AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jansetaskin.github.io/janset_website/pages/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Coming soon </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
